<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="app_name">Scuba Tanks</string>
	<string name="cylinder_size_list">Scuba Tank Sizes</string>
	<string name="edit_cylinder">Edit Cylinder Size</string>
	<string name="create_cylinder">New Cyinder Size</string>
	<string name="select_cylinder">Select a Tank Size:</string>
	<string name="create_new">New</string>
	<string name="edit">Edit</string>
	<string name="delete">Delete</string>
	<string name="luxfer_aluminum_80">Aluminum 80 (Luxfer)</string>
	<string name="double_steel_95s">"Double LP 95's"</string>
	<string name="name_prompt">Name:</string>
	<string name="internal_volume_prompt">Internal Volume</string>
	<string name="capacity_prompt">Capacity</string>
	<string name="serv_pressure_prompt">Service Pressure</string>
	<string name="volume_imperial">in<sup><small>3</small></sup>:</string>
	<string name="volume_metric">L:</string>
	<string name="capacity_imperial">ft<sup><small>3</small></sup>:</string>
	<string name="capacity_metric">L:</string>
	<string name="pres_imperial">psi:</string>
	<string name="pres_metric">bar:</string>
	<string name="imperial">US</string>
	<string name="metric">Metric</string>
	<string name="ok">OK</string>
	<string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
	<string name="help">Help</string>
	<string name="switch_to_metric">Metric</string>
	<string name="switch_to_imperial">Imperial</string>
	<string name="about">About</string>
	<string name="about_text">%1$s v%2$s
		\n\nCopyright 2009 Ben Roberts. divestoclimb@gmail.com.

		\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
		you may not use any part of this distribution except in
		compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the
		License at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless
		required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
		distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS"
		BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either
		express or implied. See the License for the specific language
		governing permissions and limitations under the License.
		
		\n\nThanks to Marcus Sundberg for providing common cylinder capacities
		in metric.
	</string>
	<string name="help_edit">About Cylinder Sizes</string>
	<string name="help_edit_text">In order to store a cylinder size, you must
		choose a name, set the fill pressure, and specify how big the cylinder is.
		Size can be set in two ways:

		\n\nIf you know the <b>internal volume</b> of the cylinder, enter that. Cylinder
		manufacturers usually have this number in their specifications, and
		divers outside of the U.S. tend to think of their cylinder size this way
		anyway. If you are using this size for gas blending, you will get the most
		accurate results by setting this number.

		\n\nDivers in the U.S. and surrounding areas consider cylinder size in terms
		of <b>capacity</b> at service pressure, e.g. an Aluminum 80 holds 80 cubic
		feet of gas. If you know only this number, you can enter it in as the
		Capacity and the internal volume will be computed. This number is not as
		accurate, though, for describing how much gas the cylinder <i>really</i>
		holds.

		\n\nIf you wish to use manifolded doubles, enter the total combined size
		of the two tanks as the "cylinder" size.

		\n\nYou can switch between imperial and metric for all cylinders by pressing
		the <b>Menu</b> button on the list screen. The units button on the edit
		screen lets you switch back and forth temporarily, but it will not save
		for next time.
	</string>
</resources>
